Register of the Albert C. Wedemeyer papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1927-1988 (Boxes 24-70)
  - Chen, Chih-mai and Lilyan, 1957-1980 (Box-folder 30: 20)
  - Chen, Victor G., 1978 (Box-folder 30: 21)
  - Cheng, Kai-min, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Cheng, Rose, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Chennault, Claire and Anna, 1958-1980 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Chiang, Ching-kuo, 1953-1988 (Box-folder 31: 4)
    Includes speeches by Chiang.
  - Chiang, Kai-shek and Chiang Soong Mei-ling, 1951-1988 (Box-folder 31: 5-6)
  - Chiang, Yun-tien, 1951-1972 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Chiang, Wego Wei-kuo, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Chickering, Sherman, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Chien, Frederick and Julie, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 31: 10)
    Includes a letter to Cyrus Vance.
  - Chien, Ta-chun, 1960-1980 (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Child, Julia, 1983 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - Chiles, H. E., 1976-1982 (Box-folder 31: 13)
  - China Airlines, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 14)
  - Chinese Culture University, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - Chinese Information Service (I-Cheng Loh), 1964-1973 (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - Chou, En-lai, 1963 (Box-folder 31: 17)
  - Chow, George and Bessie, 1964-1987 (Box-folder 31: 18)
  - Chow, Shu-kai and Lily, 1965-1988 (Box-folder 31: 19)
  - Christenberry, Chris, 1976 (Box-folder 31: 20)
  - Christensen, W. E., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31: 21)
  - Christopher, George, 1959 (Box-folder 31: 22)
  - Church, John I., 1977-1988 (Box-folder 31: 23)
  - Citizens Councils of America, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 31: 24)
  - Clagett, Page Bowie, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 31: 25)
  - Clark, Deena, 1969 (Box-folder 31: 26)
  - Clark, J. J. and Olga, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 31: 27)
    Includes letters to others.
  - Clark, Mark W., 1956-1979 (Box-folder 31: 28)
    Includes correspondence with James F. Byrnes and others.
  - Clarke, Bruce C., 1970-1980 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Clay, Lucius, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Clement, M. W., 1951-1959 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Clifford, Robert L., 1982-1988 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    Includes writings by Clifford.
  - Clostermann, Adelbert G., 1962-1985 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Coblentz, Edmond D., 1952-1958 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Cohn, Roy, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Colby, Elbridge, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Colby, William E., 1973-1987 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Coleman, Hughe, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Collier, John H., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Collins, James L., 1971-1982 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Collins, Michael, 1975 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Committee for a New Continental Congress, 1975 (Box-folder 32: 14)
  - Committee on Pan American Policy (Harold Lord Varney), 1965-1977 (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Conklin, Edward M., Jr., 1963-1968 (Box-folder 32: 16)
  - Connally, John B., 1973 (Box-folder 32: 17)
  - Conservative Party of New York State, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32: 18)
  - Cook, Christa H., 1962-1988 (Box-folder 32: 19)
  - Cooke, Charles M., 1959-1962 (Box-folder 32: 20)
  - Coordination Council for North American Affairs, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 32: 21)
  - Copley, James S. and Helen, 1959-1984 (Box-folder 32: 22)
  - Corcoran, Thomas G., 1979 (Box-folder 32: 23)
  - Corkern, Robert, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 32: 24)
  - Cornell, Robert, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 32: 25)
  - Coughenour, Richard W., 1970-1975 (Box-folder 32: 26)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1973 (Box-folder 32: 27)
  - Cox, Thomas D., 1982-1987 (Box-folder 32: 28)
  - Crane, Philip M., 1971-1987 (Box-folder 32: 29)
  - Crawford, Frederick C., 1980 (Box-folder 32: 30)
  - Creel, George, 1951-1981 (Box-folder 32: 31-32)
  - Creighton Preparatory School, 1962-1988 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Cress, James Bell, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Crittenberger, Willis D., 1952-1956 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Cromwell, James H. R., 1957-1964 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Crone, Richard I., 1965-1987 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Cronk, Walter, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Cronkite, Walter, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Crosby, William H., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Cuban Freedom Committee, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Cunningham, Harry F., 1956-1959 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Cupp, Marna M., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Currey, John Causten, 1965-1982 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Curtin, Enos, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Curtis, Carl, 1962-1985 (Box-folder 33: 14-15)
    Includes speeches by Curtis.
  - D - General, 1951-1988 (Box-folder 34: 1-2)
  - Dall, Curtis B. and Katharine, 1958-1981 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Daly, Emmet, 1962-1981 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Dannels, Ward W., 1963-1971 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Darby, Riggs, 1964-1985 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1959-1980 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Daughters of the United States Army, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Davenport, Harold A., 1980-1987 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Davidson, Darrell, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - Davidson, Garrison, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - Davidson, Howard C., 1968-1975 (Box-folder 34: 12)
  - Davie, May, 1958-1972 (Box-folder 34: 13)
    See also: SUBJECT FILE/Taft, Robert A.
  - Davis, George, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 34: 14)
  - Davis, John F., Jr., 1972-1975 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Dean, Anthony, 1970 (Box-folder 34: 16)
  - Dean, David, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 34: 17)
  - De la Guardia, Guillermo, 1963 (Box-folder 34: 18)
  - Delaney, Robert F., 1962-1973 (Box-folder 34: 19)
  - Delta Phi Epsilon, 1962-1986 (Box-folder 34: 20)
  - Del Valle, P. A., 1956 (Box-folder 34: 21)
  - Denfield, Louis, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 34: 22)
  - Denney, Robert V., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 34: 23)
  - Dennis, Lawrence, 1973 (Box-folder 34: 24)
  - Densford, Charles F., 1972-1985 (Box-folder 34: 25)
  - Dent, Frederick, 1974 (Box-folder 34: 26)
  - Devers, Jacob L., 1958-1976 (Box-folder 34: 27)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1951-1962 (Box-folder 34: 28)
  - Dickerson, Alice, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 34: 29)
  - Dickson, Benjamin A., 1972 (Box-folder 34: 30)
  - Diehl, Frances, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 34: 31)
  - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 34: 32)
  - Disney, Walter, 1956 (Box-folder 34: 33)
  - Dixon, Jeane, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 34: 34)
  - Dobson, Adna, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 34: 35)
  - Dobson, Alice, 1967-1987 (Box-folder 34: 36)
  - Dobson, Robert, 1957-1980 (Box-folder 34: 37)
  - Dodd, Thomas, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 34: 38)
  - Dodge, Joseph M., 1953-1957 (Box-folder 34: 39)
  - Doering, Otto C., Jr., 1967-1971 (Box-folder 34: 40)
  - Dominey, John V., 1971-1987 (Box-folder 34: 41)
  - Dominick, Peter H., 1966-1971 (Box-folder 34: 42)
  - Donahue, Phil, 1980 (Box-folder 34: 43)
  - Dvnitz, Karl, 1957 (Box-folder 34: 44)
  - Doolittle, James H., 1964-1985 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Drachkovitch, Milorad, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Dresser, Robert B., 1963 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Dressler, Hermann, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Drumright, Everett F., 1960-1988 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Drury, Frederick W., 1958-1978 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Dubridge, Lee A., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Duff, James Arthur, 1957-1988 (Box-folder 35: 8-9)
    Includes writings by Duff, including material relating to China.
  - Duisberg, Claus-Jrgen, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Dulles, Allen, 1961 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Dumbrille, Philip N., 1956-1975 (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Duncan, Charles V., 1988 (Box-folder 35: 13)
  - Dunn, Ju-mou, 1967 (Box-folder 35: 14)
  - Dunning, John R., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 35: 15)
  - DuPont, Marcella, 1957-1966 (Box-folder 35: 16)
  - Durant, Will, 1951-1975 (Box-folder 35: 17)
  - Duval, Miles, 1963-1982 (Box-folder 35: 18)
  - E - General, 1957-1987 (Box-folder 35: 19)
  - Eadon, Nicholas, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 35: 20)
  - Eaker, Ira, 1964-1985 (Box-folder 35: 21)
  - Earle, George H., 1958 (Box-folder 35: 22)
  - East, John P., 1985 (Box-folder 35: 23)
  - Eastman, Max, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 35: 24)
  - Echols, M. Patton, Jr., 1962-1985 (Box-folder 34: 25)
  - Edison, Charles, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Edwards, Lee, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Eichelberger, Robert L., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Eiler, Keith, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1951-1969 (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - Elia, Joseph C., 1977-1988 (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - Elkins, Wilson H., 1976 (Box-folder 36: 7)
  - Eller, Ernest M., 1962-1979 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Ellery, Mary Ann, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 36: 9)
  - Ellsworth, D. W., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - Emanuel, Barton, 1951-1972 (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - Emerson, Earl and Liette, 1962-1981 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - Emmerson, John, 1951 (Box-folder 36: 13)
  - Eng, Horace and Marguerite, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 36: 14)
  - Enloe, Cortez F., Jr., 1956-1982 (Box-folder 36: 15)
  - Exon, J. James, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 16)
  - F - General, 1956-1987 (Box-folder 36: 17)
  - Fagan, Myron C., 1954-1956 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    Includes correspondence with James Robertson and George Stratemeyer.
  - Fair, Howard, 1967 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., 1982 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Fane, Mimi, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Fannin, Paul, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - Farago, Ladislas, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - Faris, Barry, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 37: 7)
  - Farley, James A., 1956-1958 (Box-folder 37: 8)
  - Farrell, Francis and Anne, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 37: 9)
  - Fellers, Bonner, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 37: 10)
  - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 37: 11)
  - Ferger, Roger H., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 37: 12)
  - Ferrin, Charles S., 1962-1970 (Box-folder 37: 13)
  - Fertig, Lawrence, 1958-1971 (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1963-1980 (Box-folder 37: 15)
  - Fisher, Ralph T., 1964-1985 (Box-folder 37: 16)
  - Fitch, George and Geraldine, 1957-1972 (Box-folder 37: 17)
  - Fleming, John F., 1966-1970 (Box-folder 37: 18)
  - Fleming, Robert, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 37: 19)
    Includes a letter to Melville Grosvenor.
  - Flory, Lester D., 1959-1987 (Box-folder 37: 20)
  - Flower, Milton, 1965-1988 (Box-folder 37: 21)
  - Flowers, James P., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 37: 22)
  - Flynn, John T., 1958 (Box-folder 37: 23)
  - Foley, Thomas E., 1965-1969 (Box-folder 37: 24)
  - Folkes, Mary, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 37: 25)
  - Follis, R. G., 1965 (Box-folder 37: 26)
  - Fong, Hiram, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 27)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1965-1974 (Box-folder 37: 28)
  - Ford, John, 1956-1973 (Box-folder 37: 29)
  - Forrester, Eugene P., 1979-1987 (Box-folder 37: 30)
  - Fortune, 1962-1983 (Box-folder 37: 31)
  - Foster, John M., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 37: 32)
    Includes correspondence with John M. Allison, Max Bishop, Henry A. Byroade, Everett F. Drumright, Homer Ferguson, Louis Lemnitzer, William McAfee, and William T. Turner.
  - Fox, Charles R., 1970-1988 (Box-folder 37: 33)
  - Freedom Documents Foundation, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 37: 34)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge (Harold K. Johnson, Kenneth Wells and others), 1962-1972 (Box-folder 37: 35)
  - Fritz, Emanuel, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 37: 36)
  - Fuenning, Esther, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 37: 37)
  - Fu-Jen Catholic University Foundation, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 37: 38)
  - Fulks, McKendree G., 1982-1985 (Box-folder 37: 39)
  - Fuller, J. F. C., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 37: 40)
  - Fuller, Joseph W., 1970-1989 (Box-folder 37: 41)
  - Funada, Yuzuru, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 37: 42)
  - G - General, 1956-1988 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Gallagher, Philip E., 1962-1976 (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - Gannett, Frank and Caroline, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - Gard, Robert G., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Garner, Robert L., 1959-1974 (Box-folder 38: 5)
  - Garside, B. A., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    Includes writing by Garside.
  - Garvey, Willard W., 1966-1971 (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - Gavin, James M., 1965-1972 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Gayle, Richard B., 1957-1977 (Box-folder 38: 9)
  - Gayle, Richard B., Jr., 1974-1985 (Box-folder 38: 10)
  - George, Alex and Louise, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - George, Walter, 1952 (Box-folder 38: 12)
  - Gerard, James W., 1966-1973 (Box-folder 38: 13)
  - German American National Congress, 1983 (Box-folder 38: 14)
  - Gerow, Leonard T., 1958-1986 (Box-folder 38: 15)
  - Giannini, L. M., 1951-1952 (Box-folder 38: 16)
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1951 (Box-folder 38: 17)
  - Gigleman, Gay, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 38: 18)
  - Gill, William J., 1971-1988 (Box-folder 38: 19)
  - Ginsberg, Israel, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 38: 20)
  - Godfrey, Arthur, 1959 (Box-folder 38: 21)
  - Goldsborough, Robert H., 1975-1979 (Box-folder 38: 22)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 38: 23)
    See also: SUBJECT FILE/United States-Politics and Government/1964 Presidential election/Goldwater, Barry.
  - Goock, Roland, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 38: 24)
  - Good, Lara P., 1962-1975 (Box-folder 38: 25)
    Includes writings by Good.
  - Goodale, George S., 1984-1986 (Box-folder 38: 26)
  - Goodpaster, Andrew J., 1975-1985 (Box-folder 38: 27)
  - Goodyear, William and Hettie, 1962-1979 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - Grace, W. Porter, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 39: 2)
  - Graham, Billy, 1975 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - Grant, Harold W., 1981-1987 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Grasse, William, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Graves, Sidney C., 1957-1968 (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - Greaves, Percy L., Jr., 1962-1982 (Box-folder 39: 7)
    See also: SPEECHES AND WRITINGS/Foreword, 1984
  - Green, William F., 1981-1987 (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Grenata, Michael C., 1967-1988 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Grew, Joseph, 1956 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - Griffin, Robert B., 1966 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - Griffith, John S., 1976-1979 (Box-folder 39: 12)
  - Gros, Robert R., 1958-1985 (Box-folder 39: 13)
  - Groves, Leslie R., 1965-1970 (Box-folder 39: 14)
  - Gruenther, Alfred, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 39: 15)
  - Grundy, Arthur, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 39: 16)
  - Gude, Gilbert, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 39: 17)
  - Gunner, Matthew J., 1958-1971 (Box-folder 39: 18)
  - H - General, 1951-1988 (Box-folder 39: 19-21)
  - Haig, Alexander M., Jr., 1976-1987 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Halder, Franz, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Hall, Irving, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - Halla, Mitzi and Brien, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Hamilton, Edith, 1951-1958? (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - Handy, Thomas T., 1974-1980 (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - Hansell, Haywood S., 1973-1988 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Hansen, Clifford P., 1971 (Box-folder 40: 8)
  - Hardin, John, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 40: 9)
  - Harper, John S., 1962-1971 (Box-folder 40: 10)
  - Harrington, David O., 1956-1982 (Box-folder 40: 11)
  - Harris, Calvin, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 40: 12)
  - Harris, Thomas J., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 40: 13)
  - Harriss, Robert M., 1957-1964 (Box-folder 40: 14)
  - Hartness, Harlan N., 1976-1983 (Box-folder 40: 15)
  - Harvey, Paul, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40: 16)
  - Harwood, E. C., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 40: 17)
  - Hasbrouck, Robert W., 1973-1984 (Box-folder 40: 18)
  - Hastings, Kester A., 1970-1983 (Box-folder 40: 19)
  - Hastings, Peter, 1956-1987 (Box-folder 40: 20)
  - Hatch, Orrin, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 21)
  - Hau, Pei-tsun, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 40: 22)
  - Hazlitt, Henry, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 40: 23)
  - Heard, Townsend, 1958-1988 (Box-folder 40: 24)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1958-1976 (Box-folder 40: 25)
  - Heaton, Leonard D., 1951-1980 (Box-folder 40: 26)
  - Hebb, Angus G., 1965-1988 (Box-folder 40: 27)
  - Heerema, Pieter S., 1977-1986 (Box-folder 40: 28)
  - Helberg, James C., 1983-1988 (Box-folder 40: 29)
  - Helms, Richard, 1967 (Box-folder 40: 30)
  - Henle, Ray, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 40: 31)
  - Henning, Frank A., 1975-1979 (Box-folder 40: 32)
  - Heppner, Richard P., 1954-1985 (Box-folder 40: 33)
  - Hermann, Mogens V., 1979 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1958 (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - Hewes, Clarence B., 1951 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - Hill, A. G., 1959-1976 (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - Hill, John W., 1956-1970 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Hill, Richard J., Jr., 1980 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - Hill, Robert A., 1982-1985 (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Hillsdale College, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - Hirsch, Maurice, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - Ho, Shai-lai, 1973 (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - Ho, Ying-chin, 1952-1985 (Box-folder 41: 11)
    Includes speeches and writings by Ho.
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1982 (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - Hodes, Henry, 1957 (Box-folder 41: 13)
  - Hoffman, Claire Giannini, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 41: 14)
  - Hogg, Robert L., 1956-1968 (Box-folder 41: 15)
  - Holbrook, Willard A., Jr., 1964-1985 (Box-folder 41: 16)
  - Holle, Charles G., 1968-1976 (Box-folder 41: 17)
  - Holloway, Hubert, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 41: 18)
  - Hoover, Allan, 1951-1981 (Box-folder 41: 19)
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1951-1964 (Box-folder 41: 20-21)
    Includes speeches by Hoover.
  - Hoover, Herbert C., Jr., 1951-1969 (Box-folder 41: 22)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1951-1967 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Hope, Bob, 1976 (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Hopper, Hedda, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 42: 3)
  - Horn, Thomas L. and Dorothy, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1959-1966 (Box-folder 42: 5)
  - Hottenstein, Daisy, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 42: 6)
  - Houpt, William P., 1981-1987 (Box-folder 42: 7)
  - Howard, Roy W., 1955-1964 (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - Howley, Frank L., 1957-1964 (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Hoyne, R. E., 1977 (Box-folder 42: 10)
  - Hruska, Roman L., 1968-1977 (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Hsi, Chen-yun, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Hu, Shu-kuang, 1961-1983 (Box-folder 42: 13)
  - Huang, David D., 1963-1973 (Box-folder 42: 14)
  - Huang, Jen-lin, 1959-1981 (Box-folder 42: 15)
    Includes speeches by Huang.
  - Hubbard, Bernard R., 1951-1956 (Box-folder 42: 16)
  - Hukel, Lena Miemietz, 1959 (Box-folder 42: 17)
  - Hughes, Howard, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 42: 18)
  - Huling, John, Jr., 1976-1986 (Box-folder 42: 19)
  - Hull, John E., 1962-1975 (Box-folder 42: 20)
  - Human Events, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 42: 21)
  - Humphries, Paul Douglas, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 42: 22)
    Includes correspondence with William Casey and others.
  - Hunt, H. L., 1952-1985 (Box-folder 42: 23)
    Includes letters by others and speeches by Hunt.
  - Hunt, Nelson Bunker, 1956-1982 (Box-folder 42: 24)
  - Hunter, Charles N., 1962-1972 (Box-folder 42: 25)
  - Hurley, Patrick J., 1955-1963 (Box-folder 42: 26)
  - Huston, Milburn N., 1965-1985 (Box-folder 42: 27)
  - Hutchin, Claire and Kitty, 1959-1980 (Box-folder 42: 28)
  - Hutchinson, Homer C., 1979-1987 (Box-folder 42: 29)
  - Hutton, E. F., 1954-1959 (Box-folder 42: 30)
  - Hutton, Tom, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 42: 31)
  - I - General, 1967-1982 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - Imprimis, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - Information Council of the Americas, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, 1966-1982 (Box-folder 43: 4)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 43: 5)
  - Ismay, Hastings, 1957 (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - Ittensohn, Jacques, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 43: 7)
  - J - General, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 43: 8)
  - Jackson, Charles R., 1965 (Box-folder 43: 9)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1962-1969 (Box-folder 43: 10)
  - Jarrell, John W., 1958-1971 (Box-folder 43: 11)
  - Javits, Jacob, 1971 (Box-folder 43: 12)
  - Jenner, William E., 1952-1959 (Box-folder 43: 13)
  - Jennings, John Q., 1971-1986
    Includes letters by Henry Hazlitt, Alfred E. Kahn, and Ronald Reagan.
    - 1971-1980 (Box-folder 43: 14-16)
    - 1980-1986 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Johansing, Paul and Bette, 1957-1977 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - Johnson, Albert Sidney, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - Johnson, Douglas V., 1972-1977 (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1958 (Box-folder 44: 5)
  - Johnson, Robert L., 1955-1964 (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Johnson, Robert W., 1959-1964 (Box-folder 44: 7)
  - Johnson, Theodore R., 1959-1966 (Box-folder 44: 8)
  - Johnson, Thomas M., 1957-1965 (Box-folder 44: 9)
  - Johnson, Victor A., circa 1958 (Box-folder 44: 10)
  - Jones, Charles Hill, 1964-1976 (Box-folder 44: 11)
  - Jones, Herbert M., 1957-1986 (Box-folder 44: 12)
  - Jones, Homer H., 1962-1985 (Box-folder 44: 13)
  - Jones, John M., 1985-1986 (Box-folder 44: 14)
  - Jones, Mark, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 44: 15)
  - Jones, Orren L., 1968-1975 (Box-folder 44: 16)
  - Jones, Proctor, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 44: 17)
  - Jones, Robert Letts, 1959-1976 (Box-folder 44: 18)
  - Jones, Thomas W., 1964-1969 (Box-folder 44: 19)
  - Jones, Wyly K., 1968-1980 (Box-folder 44: 20)
  - Jonker, Frederick, 1976 (Box-folder 44: 21)
    Includes writings by Jonker.
  - Judd, Walter, 1954-1985 (Box-folder 44: 22)
    Includes speeches by Judd.
  - K - General, 1953-1988 (Box-folder 44: 23)
  - Kahle, Louise, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 44: 24)
  - Kahn, Alfred E., 1980 (Box-folder 44: 25)
  - Kaisch, Charles E., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 44: 26)
  - Kaltenborn, H. V., 1958 (Box-folder 44: 27)
  - Kam, Edwin, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 44: 28)
  - Kao, Lindberg, 1968 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - Kearney State College, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - Keen, Chuck D., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - Kelland, Clarence Budington, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - Kelley, Anne, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 45: 5)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L., 1978 (Box-folder 45: 6)
  - Kemna, Christine and Axel, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 45: 7)
  - Kemp, Arthur, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 45: 8)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Kemper, James S., 1956-1968 (Box-folder 45: 10)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1966 (Box-folder 45: 11)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1958 (Box-folder 45: 12)
  - Kent, Graham Gunther, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 45: 13)
  - Kernan, Redmond and Peggy, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 45: 14)
  - Kesselring, Albert, 1953 (Box-folder 45: 15)
  - Kiley, John Cantwell, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 45: 16)
    Includes a letter by William F. Buckley.
  - Kilpatrick, James J., 1971 (Box-folder 45: 17)
  - Kilroy, George, 1956-1966 (Box-folder 45: 18)
  - Kim, H. C., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 45: 19)
  - Kirby, Patrick James, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 45: 20)
  - Kirk, Neville T., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 45: 21)
  - Kirk, Russell, 1981 (Box-folder 45: 22)
  - Kleffens, Eelco N. van, 1954 (Box-folder 45: 23)
  - Knezevich, Zivan L., 1967-1979 (Box-folder 45: 24)
  - Knight [Parrish], Frances G., 1972-1977 (Box-folder 45: 25)
  - Knorpp, Walter W., 1963-1970 (Box-folder 45: 26)
  - Knott, Walter, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 45: 27)
  - Knowland, William F., 1951-1964 (Box-folder 45: 28)
  - Knowlton, William A., 1970-1980 (Box-folder 45: 29)
  - Koch, Fred C., 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45: 30)
  - Kohlbeck, LeRoy E., 1967-1974 (Box-folder 45: 31)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1951-1968 (Box-folder 45: 32)
    Includes a letter to Kohlberg by Archibald Roosevelt.
  - Komisarjevsky, Christopher P. A., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 45: 33)
  - Koo, Wellington, 1952-1985 (Box-folder 45: 34)
  - Koster, Samuel W., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 45: 35)
  - Krause, George H., 1956-1958 (Box-folder 45: 36)
  - Kreuz, Frank P., 1956-1966 (Box-folder 45: 37)
  - Krock, Arthur, 1968 (Box-folder 45: 38)
  - Krueger, William C., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - Krulak, Victor H., 1968-1974 (Box-folder 46: 2)
  - Kubek, Anthony, 1958-1986 (Box-folder 46: 3)
    Includes writings by Kubek.
  - Kuhn, Irene Corbally, 1958-1988 (Box-folder 46: 4)
    Includes writings by Kuhn.
  - Kung, H. H., 1956-1967 (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - Kung, Ling-kai, 1967-1987 (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - Kusumowidagdo, Suwito, 1967 (Box-folder 46: 7)
  - L - General, 1955-1988 (Box-folder 46: 8-9)
  - LaFollette, Suzanne, 1952 (Box-folder 46: 10)
  - Lai, Ming-tong, 1976 (Box-folder 46: 11)
  - Laird, Melvin, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 46: 12)
    Includes a letter by Richard Ware.
  - Lamont, Elizabeth B., 1976-1983 (Box-folder 46: 13)
  - Lanham, C. T., 1966 (Box-folder 46: 14)
  - Lassner, Franz G., 1965-1980 (Box-folder 46: 15)
  - Lattimore, Walter, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 46: 16)
  - Lau, Milton, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 46: 17)
  - Lausche, Frank J., 1965 (Box-folder 46: 18)
  - Lawrence, David, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 46: 19)